elections.gov.hk 2019-11-28

# 2019 District Council Election - Privacy Policy

The Government of the Hong Kong Special Administrative Region ("the Government") is concerned to ensure that all personal data submitted through elections.gov.hk are handled in accordance with the relevant provisions of the [Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance](https://www.pcpd.org.hk/english/data_privacy_law/ordinance_at_a_Glance/ordinance.html).

The Government will record visits to elections.gov.hk without collecting any personal identifiable information of users. Such general statistics are collected for the compilation of statistical reports and the diagnosis of problems with or concerning computer systems to help improve elections.gov.hk.

For different purposes and at different times you may be invited to provide personal data to the Government through elections.gov.hk on a voluntary basis. Personal information may include name, telephone number, mailing address or e-mail address. The Government will specify the collection purpose and intended usage of your data when it invites you to provide such information and advise you how you may request access to or correction of the personal data provided.

Unless permitted or required by law, the Government will not disclose your personal data to any third parties without your prior consent.

The search service on elections.gov.hk is provided by an independent contractor of the Government. We are advised by the independent contractor that it does not collect personal identifiable information while serving search results through elections.gov.hk. The independent contractor will share the anonymous data it collects through the search service with the Government for compiling traffic analysis on government websites. The Government will not match the data obtained from any such search activity with any personal data possibly held by the Government.
